yr.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

**YR.com Privacy & Policies**

**Last updated – May 10, 2019**

This website is operated by Young & Rubicam Brands (“Y&R”, "we" or "us"). **By using and visiting our website and by submitting your information to us, you agree to us using your information as set out in this privacy policy.** This Privacy Policy applies solely to the website located at YR.com and not to any other website or service.

[If you just want to know about how we use cookies please click here](http://www.wpp.com/wpp/cookies.htm).

We respect the privacy of users of our website and recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner with that information. This privacy policy contains important information about how we use your personal information.

**What information do we collect?**

At times you may voluntarily choose to supply us with personal information, such as when emailing us from the “Contact Us” page or applying for employment with us. In such instances, we may gather the following information about you:

Name  
Email address  
Telephone number  
IP address (a unique identifier for your computer or other device)  
Mobile device ID  
Information provided by you in relation to submitting a job application to us (this may include sensitive personal information e.g. ethnic origin)

**How do we use it?**

We will use this information in the following ways:

  * to provide you with information that you have requested (e.g. a newsletter, bulletins);
  * to respond to specific queries you may raise regarding Y&R;
  * to provide you with better ways of accessing information from this website;
  * to process and consider your job application; and
  * as otherwise disclosed to you at the time such information is collected.

For how we use your information that is collected using cookies and similar technologies please see the "Cookies" section [here](http://www.wpp.com/wpp/cookies.htm).

**Do we pass your information to third parties?**

We may send your personal information to our affiliated companies if the nature of your request requires us to do so. We may also use third party vendors to help us process your personal information for the purposes set out in this policy, but they are not authorized by us to use your personal information for their own purposes.

We may disclose your personal information if we or any of our assets are the subject of a sale or similar corporate transaction.

We may disclose personal information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are required by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual unlawful or otherwise prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud.

**How do we use your information for marketing?**

We will only provide information to you that you have asked for via the website.

**Where do we send your information?**

We are a global company and therefore we may transfer your personal information to countries around the world including the United States and other countries outside Europe. We will, where necessary, put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure your information is protected.

**How long do we keep your information?**

We will keep your information for a reasonable period for the purposes set out above.

**Cookies**

**What are cookies?**

We may use information obtained from cookies or similar technology. Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are stored by your computer or device when you visit our website. Therefore, when we refer to "you" in this section we mean your computer. We can recognize these cookies on subsequent visits and they allow us to remember you.

Cookies come in many forms. We have set out below the main types and categories of cookies that are used. This section refers to all types and categories of cookies and not just those we use on our website.

**First and third-party cookies** \- whether a cookie is first-party or third-party refers to the domain placing the cookie. First-party cookies are those set by a website that is being visited by the user, the website displayed in the URL window e.g. [www.yr.com](http://www.yr.com/) . Third-Party cookies are cookies that are set by a domain other than that of the website being visited by the user. If a user visits a website and another entity sets a cookie through that website this would be a third-party cookie.

**Persistent cookies** – these cookies remain on a user's device for the period of time specified at the time the website requested the cookie to be set. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.

**Session cookie** – these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted.

**What do we use cookies for?**

Cookies can fall into one or more of the categories. This website uses cookies which may fall into the following two categories set forth below.

**1\. Strictly necessary cookies – These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for.**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies certain services you have asked for cannot be provided.

**2\. Performance cookies – These cookies collect information on the pages visited.**

These cookies collect information about how users use a website, for instance which pages users go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. Such cookies may include third party cookies provided by Google and Yahoo analytics. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and not used by us to identify individual users. They are only used to improve how the website works.

If you want to delete any cookies that may already be on your computer or device, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. If you want to stop cookies being stored on your computer in future, please refer to your browser manufacturer’s instructions by clicking “Help” in your browser menu. Further information on cookies is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our website.

**Links to Third Party Websites**

Our website may link to third party sites which we do not operate or endorse. These websites may use cookies and collect your information in accordance with their own privacy policies. This privacy policy does not apply to third party websites and we are not responsible for third party websites. Such third party websites may include websites of companies who are affiliated with Y&R, but have their own privacy practices and disclosures.

**Social Media Sites**

Our website may use links or tools from social media services, such as a “Like” or “Share” button. We do not control such services or how they use your information. By using such features you acknowledge that Y&R is not responsible for how such social media services track you or use your information and you will be subject to the applicable social media provider’s privacy practices and disclosures.

**How do we protect your information?**

We take appropriate measures to ensure that your personal information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used.

**Under 13 year olds** This website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from or about any person under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old and wish to ask a question or use this website in any way which requires you to submit your personal information, please get your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.

**How to obtain a copy of your information**

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the personal information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to have any inaccuracies in your personal information corrected. Please contact us using the details set out below.

**How to contact us if your information or choices change**

If your personal information or your preferences change, you don't want us to send you the information you have requested or if you have any queries about how we use your personal information, please let us know by contacting our Compliance Officer at [privacy@yr.com](mailto:privacy@yr.com).

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this privacy policy at any time. You are encouraged to review this privacy policy from time to time.

**Questions**

If you have any questions about the privacy practices of this website, you may contact us at [privacy@yr.com](mailto:privacy@yr.com)

**Due Diligence In Our Business**

Y&R does not tolerate any form of modern slavery or human trafficking in any part of our business. Y&R is a subsidiary of WPP, therefore please refer to [WPP’s Modern Slavery statement here](https://urldefense.proofpoint.com/v2/url?u=https-3A__www.wpp.com_sustainability_&d=DwMFaQ&c=qwStF0e4-YFyvjCeML3ehA&r=MQ7IHdbl9zUuldyzTFtXmE9Un9Kd3gaJqXkSpYQDHco&m=1auC_z0Ljggjk2drX5qxJo_s1EuQWRxtXb89czndcbY&s=L7dYxjxYDqHDZ7c0BQ1cEUcoF8u-8sgb84NvTzZItHg&e=).
